For brands like yours, preventing customers from receiving counterfeits is a top priority.
And protecting customers, brands, and sellers is incredibly important at Amazon.
Amazon strictly prohibits the sale of counterfeit products,
and our customers expect that when they make a purchase,
either directly from Amazon or one of its millions of third-party sellers,
they'll receive authentic products.
That's why we launched Amazon Project Zero.
By combining our advanced technology, machine learning, and innovation
with your expert knowledge of your own intellectual property and products,
we can work together with your brand to drive counterfeits to zero.
Here's how it works.
Once you join Project Zero, just provide trademarks, logos,
and other key data points about your brand,
and our automated protections scan billions of attempted listing updates every day
to find and remove suspected counterfeits before they're added to our stores.
These protections are continuously fed new information,
so we constantly get better at automatically preventing
and blocking potential counterfeit listings.
And if you do spot a counterfeit listing,
you'll have the unprecedented ability to remove it yourself immediately
without the need to contact us.
These removals help our automated protections get smarter and stronger, too.
You can also choose to enroll some or all of your products
in our optional serialization service.
Applying a unique code to each unit you manufacture
allows us to easily scan and confirm the authenticity
of every item listed and purchased in our stores,
stopping counterfeits before they reach customers.
While this is optional, enrolled brands see the best results
when using our serialization technology.
Tens of thousands of brands are now enrolled in Project Zero,
working with Amazon to eliminate counterfeits.
To learn more, visit projectzero.
com.
Protect your brand with Amazon.